Kavinda Adithya

+9477-037-0909 • kiwiyaaa@gmail.com • kavinda.vercel.app

Developer/Designer

I am a Frontend Developer with a talent for creating immersive interfaces using HTML, CSS, and React, with specialized expertise in Next.js. My approach blends technical prowess with creative finesse to deliver outstanding user experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IMI Games • June 2022 - Present

Product Manager

- User Experience (UX) and Design Enhanced user experience through strategic design improvements.
- Client Queries and Releases Managed product releases and handled client inquiries.
- Cross-Functional Collaboration Worked with various teams to achieve project goals.
- Agile Development Led agile processes and sprint planning.

ShoutOUT Labs • June 2018 - May 2022 Front End Engineer

- Front End Development & Responsive Design Developed responsive web applications to ensure optimal performance on various devices.
- UI/UX Implementation & Integration Translated wireframes into intuitive and beautiful user interfaces, enhancing user experience.
- Wireframing and Implementation Worked from wireframing the product to improve user experience, building and implementing intuitive UIs to enhance platform performance.

EDUCATION

MSc in IT & Strategic Innovation

Kingston University • January 2023 - August 2024

- Agile Project Development
- IT and Entrepreneurship
- Databases and Data Management
- Business in Practice

Certificate Level

BCS, The Chartered Institute for IT • March 2022 - September 2022

- Information Systems
- Software Development
- Computer and Network Technology

SKILLS

- Communication & Adaptability
- Innovative & Strategic Thinking

- Problem-Solving & Collaboration Emotional Intelligence
- Continuous Learning

Technical Skills

- React
- Next.js
- HTML
- CSS
- Figma
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap
- PHP
- MySQL

AWARDS

Best Digital Enabled Product/Service (2018)